Jiss Anto

Android Developer

Contact

Address

Thrissur, Kerala, 680306

Phone

+91 8606387830

E-mail

jissanto@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://in.linkedin.com/in/jissanto-6a5215126

Skills

Programming

Technical analysis

Web development projects

Web user interfaces

Technical Support

Android development

Bug resolution

Project Management

Testing and maintenance

Hardworking software development professional driven to increase team effectiveness. Focused on usability and performance improvements. Proven history of developing useful, efficient and costeffective projects. Strong decision-maker with more than 3 years of experience in software engineering and application development. Ready to work closely with both teams and customers to identify most efficient and beneficial solutions for process improvement.

Work History

2014-07 -2015-05

IT Administrator - Intern

National Service Scheme - PENTA, Thrissur, Kerala

- Resolved issues and escalated problems with knowledgeable support and quality service.
- Standardized job tasks and trained junior team members on industry best practices and standards.
- Implemented, developed and tested installation and update of file servers.

2017-06 -2018-12

System Administrator Trainee

Jawaharlal College of Engineering & Technology, Palakkad, Kerala

- Developed team communications and information for official website development.
- Maintained excellent attendance record, consistently arriving to work on time.
- Monitored social media and online sources for industry trends.

2019-01 -Current

Software Engineer

Integrated Red Cherry Solutions Pvt. Ltd., Calicut, Kerala

- Installed and configured software applications and tested solutions for effectiveness.
- Conducted regression testing, analyzed results and submitted observations to development team.
- Worked with project managers, developers, quality assurance and customers to resolve technical issues.

Software PHP Android HTML CSS JS React JS MS Office GIMP Languages Malayalam English Tamil German

Education

2010-08 -	High School (SSLC)
2011-03	Holy Angel's HSS - Ollur, Thrissur, Kerala Secondary School Leaving Certificate of State Board,
	Kerala.
2011-08 -	High Secondary School
2013-05	Technical Higher Secondary School - Chengannur, Alappuzha, Kerala Technical Higher Secondary School Certificate from Institute of Human Resources Development (IHRD), State Board, Kerala
2013-08 - 2017-05	Bachelor of Technology: Electronics and Communications Engineering
	JCET (Calicut University) - Palakkad Course Completed only.

Certifications

2013-05 Certified Mobile Technician from Indian Technical Society.